ILGWU Communications Department Photographs 5780/176 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Samuel Gompers (Box 19, Folder 3)
  Includes Official Program of Dedication of Samuel Gompers Memorial Monument, 1933; Gompers addresses Cooper Union meeting, 1909; Gompers reading in chair; Gompers with Bob La Follete, Sr. and La Follete, Jr., 1920's; Gompers Memorial Monument; Gompers and Bob La Follete, Sr.; Gompers holding shovel at ceremony launching AFL building in Washington; Gompers with James Duncan, Frank Morrison, William Green and Valentine; Gompers with President Woodrow Wilson, at dedication ceremonies for AFL building, 1916; Executive Council luncheon for Plutaroo Elias Calles, 1924; Gompers and Charles Schwab; Gompers and delegates at first convention of the International Broom and Whisk makers Union, 1893; First meeting of International Federation of trade unions, Gompers, Daniel J. Tobin, J. J. Hynes and Guy H. Cyster, 1919; First Executive Council of AFL, Samuel Gompers, Chas F. burgmen, W. H. Foster, Alex C. Raukh and Richard Powers, 1881;National Civic Federation luncheon with Ralph M. Easley, Oscar S. Straus, C. W. Bowerman, August Belmont, Gompers, W. S. Carter, W. M. Fellowes Morgan, Joseph Davies, H. W. Garod, Elisha Lee, Haley Fiske, Warren S. Stone, 1917; Gompers in Labor Day parade, 1911; Gompers with Edgar Wallace, Guy Oyster and C. L. Baine, 1918; Gompers and his wife in Atlantic City, 1924; Gompers Postage Stamp negatives
- Personalities G (Box 19, Folder 4)
  Includes Herman Grossman; Mary Goff in Labor Day parade. 1960's; Mary Goff portrait, 1921; VP Al Gore with Sen. Judy Sassek, 1994; Murray Gross; Prof. John Kenneth Galbraith; Chief Inspector Sanford Garelih; Hugh Gaitskill at 1956 convention; Joe [Glaestone]; Alcide De Gasperi, Italian PM; Valentino Gello; Ben Gilbert addressing meeting of Missouri AFL; Morris Glushien; Sid Gerstein; Arturo Giovannitti, 1937; Arthur J. Goldberg; Arthur Goldberg and David Dubinsky, 1965; Arthur Goldberg, Dubinsky and Orville Freeman, 1965; Arthur Goldman at ILGWU executive board meeting, 1965; Joe Glazer; Max Goldenberg; Sol Goldberg; Harry Goldin; Manuel Gonzalez and Abraham Roshco; Sidney Good; Harry Greenberg; Sol Greene; William Green; Jerry Grossman; William Gomberg; Max Guzman; David Gingold presiding over Fall River, MA contract vote; Bernadine Gardiner; George Gerundo
- Personalities H (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Includes Sidney Hillam, John L. Lewis and Emil Rieve, 1939; George J. Higgins with Stephen I. Schlossberg; Jim Hightower; Han Dongfang and Jay Mazur; Sol Hoffman; Hannah Haskel; Hannah Haskel and Lazare Teper; Norman Hill, 1983; Paul Hall and Charles Zimmerman; Paul Hall; Simon Hamberger; George Harrison, 1960; Adolph Held; Harry Haskel; Phillip Heller with Karl Mantler and Anton Proksch at farewell party from Austrian Federation of Trade unions, 1951; Ailene Hernandez; Phillip Heller, Karl Mantler, Anton Prokesch and Johann Boehm, 1951
- Personalities H (Box 19, Folder 6)
  Includes - Morris Hillquit Plaque; Morris Hillquit; Will Herberg; Eleanor Hernandez; Sam Herbst; James Hoffa; Dr. Hoffman; Sol Hoffman; Herbert Hoover; Israel Horowitz, Murray Gerstein, Sadie Reisch and Irwin Suall, 1951; Ben Horowtiz; belle Horensen, 1977; Local 295 members Rita Hensley, Theresa Cumbo, Mark Dzanis, Lois Hartel, Terry Hotko and Eileen McDonnell at muscular dystrophy parade, 1985; Jacob Halpern; Julius Hochman
- Personalities I (Box 19, Folder 7)
  Includes At Manhattan Center, Wohl, Hillman, Wilkie, Harrison and Umhey, 1941
- Personalities J (Box 19, Folder 8)
  Includes Mother Jones; Charles Jacobson; Lyndon B. Johnson with ILGers; LB Johnson and Dubinsky at 50th anniversary of ILGWU Health Center; Dubinsky and Lyndon Johnson; Hubert Humphrey looks on as Lyndon Johnson signs Medicare into law; CLUW Pres. Gloria Johnson, 1995; Lillian Johnson; Henry Jackson at '71 convention; Vernon Jordan; Sam James, 1977; Henry Jackson and E. Molisani; Claude Jodoin; Lady Bird Johnson; Leon Jouhaux; Mattie Jackson, 1983; Mattie Jackson and Congressman Phil Burstow, 1982; Mattie Jackson and Lane Kirkland; Delegation to California Federation of Labor convention
- John F Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 9)
  Includes Kennedy, Dubinsky and George Meany; Kennedy and Dubinsky; Kennedy, Dubinsky and Adlai Stevenson; First meeting of Kennedy's Advisory Committee on Labor-Management Policy with Luther Hodges, Arthur Goldberg, George M. Harrison, Richard Reynolds, Dubinsky, Elliot V. Bell, Walter Reuther and John M. Franklin, 1961; Kennedy hands pen to Franklin Roosevelt, Jr. while Dubinsky, Emanuel Celler, Philip Klutznick, Anna Rosenberg, Bess Myerson and Walter Reuther look on; Kennedy Speaks to large crowd on 7th Ave.; Kennedy, Dubinsky and Fred Umhey; Kennedy discusses labor with George Meany and Senator Irving Ives, 1958; Kennedy at ILG GEB meeting; Kennedy's hand-written inaugural address notes; Jacqueline Kennedy; Kennedy speaking at AFL CIO convention; Kennedy, Dubinsky, Lyndon Johnson, George Meany, and W. Willard Wirtz at White House, 1962
- Personalities K (Box 19, Folder 10)
  Includes Robert F Kennedy and Dubinsky; Robert F. Kennedy and Dubinsky at rally, 1964; Martin Luther King and Dubinsky; Senator Ted Kennedy and ILGers from Fall River, MA, 1970; Lillian Kolwyck, 1984; Robert F Kennedy speaks while Charles Zimmerman looks on, 1964; Kearney and Bustos; Voncille Kinard spread from Justice; Joan Cummings and Helen Knight prepare for their ILG commercials, 1980
- Personalities K (Box 20, Folder 1)
  Includes - Ed Koch and Jay Mazur; Ed Kramer and Cornelius Wall, 1980; Lane Kirkland; Milt Kaplan; Dr. William H. Kilpatrick; Harry Krugman; Charles Kreindler; Alex Kahn; Abraham W. Katovsky; Abraham Kazan; Congressman George M. Rhodes and Paul Strongin welcome Senator Estes Kefauver as honorary ILG member, 1962; Al Kehrer; Nicholas Kirtzman; Samuel Klein; Murray Kolker; Ben Kaplan; Morris Kovler; Edward Kramer speaking at convention, 1960; Philip Kramer; Charles Kreindler speaking; Lester Kushner; Leo [Kesperling]; Ed Koch at ILG meeting; Don Kret; Lillian Kolwyck with James Neeley, Eddie Bryan, Clarence Frosy, Bill Pack, Annie Randall and Lillian Grobmyer
- La Guardia, Fiorello (Box 20, Folder 2)
  Includes Portraits and individual photos of La Guardia; La Guardia and Uviller; La Guardia watching the making of a button-hole; La Guardia and Danush; La Guardia and Luigi Antonini; Marie La Guardia
- Lehman, Herbert (Box 20, Folder 3)
  Includes Portraits and individual photos of Lehman,; Campaign poster; Lehman at ILG convention; Lehman with Alex Rose, George Meany and Paul Douglas
- Lemlich, Clara (Box 20, Folder 4)
  Includes Portraits of Lemlich
- Levin, Douglas (Box 20, Folder 5)
  Includes Portrait; Levin speaking
- Levy, Louis (Box 20, Folder 6)
  Includes Portrait; Levy giving bonds to Lee Gersten and Louis Tabak
- Lewis, John L (Box 20, Folder 7)
  Includes Portraits and individual photos; Lewis with Charles Zimmerman; Lewis and Sidney Hillman; Lewis awarding officer qualification awards
- Liberman, Elias (Box 20, Folder 8)
  Includes Portrait; Liberman at podium
- London, Meyer (Box 20, Folder 9)
  Includes Portrait; Memorial Plaque
- Lorgo, Frank (Box 20, Folder 10)
  Includes Portraits
- Lovestone, Jay (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Lurye, William (Box 20, Folder 12)
  Includes Portrait; Lurye's Funeral procession, 1949
- Personalities L (Box 20, Folder 13)
  Includes Winnie Lippman, Junette Turley, and Juanita Vaeth going over backpay checks, 1979; Senator Robert La Follette; James Lipsig; Lefkowitz; Mitchell Lokiec; John Lindsay; Matthew M. Levy; {Zalman} Lichtenstein and Congressman Wilbur Mills; Representative John Lewis; Pete Licausi; Morris Lanbger; Rose Mersky Levine; Christmas party, Local 155, 1984
- Maltese, Vincent (Box 20, Folder 14)
  Includes Maltese at Tenement Museum; Maltese and his family
- Markowich, Samuel (Box 20, Folder 15)
  Includes - Portraits
- Martin, John (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Mazur, Jay (Box 20, Folder 17)
  Includes Portraits and individual photos; Mazur with Chinese retirees, 1983; Mazur testifying; Maur with ILGers; Jay Mazur, Max Zinny and Evelyn Dubrow testify, 1986; Mazur presenting Francis Brunclik back pay check with Tony Sciuto and Ondina Medrano, 1980
- McCarthy, Eugene (Box 20, Folder 18)
  Includes Portrait
- Meir, Golda (Box 20, Folder 19)
  Includes Portrait; Golda Meir and Shelly Appleton, 1959; Golda Meir and George Meany, 1975
- Mendelsund, Henry (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Matheson, Min (Box 20, Folder 21)
- McKittric, Lillian (Box 20, Folder 22)
  Includes Lillian McKittric receiving portrait and plaque
- Miller, Freeda (Box 20, Folder 23)
  Includes Portrait; Miller's induction as charter member to Local 142
- Miller, Meyer (Box 20, Folder 24)
  Includes Portraits; Miller with Senator Henry Jackson, Bill Kaufman and Jim Mahoney
- Millman, Leon (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Molisani, Edwardo (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Molisani, E. Howard (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Mondale, Walter (Box 20, Folder 28)
  Includes Mondale on stage with George Meany and Sol Chaikin; Receiving award from Sol Chaikin and George Meany
- Morand, Marty (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Morse, David (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Moynihan, Patrick (Box 20, Folder 31)
  Includes Moynihan at New York state AFL CIO rally; Mondale with Judith Wineman, Lena Paterno and Robert Brown at Senate subcommittee hearing
- Munoz, Luis (Box 20, Folder 32)
  Includes Portrait; Munoz with Puerto Rican ILGers, 1957
- Personalities M (Box 20, Folder 33)
  Includes Jennie Matyas; Nathaniel B. Minkoff; Painting of Giacomo Matteolti; Wayne Morse; Newbold Morris; Herbert Morrison; Vanni Montana; Fred Umhey, Mickey Kaplan, Howard Mobrian and Joseph Breslaw, 1952; Lazar Teper, Murray Finley, George Meany and Sol Chaikin leaving White House, 1977; [Evla] McGill, 1946; George J. Mintzer; Maurice Manel; Art Martin; Nathan Margolies; Morris Makin; Jim Mahoney; Edmund Muskie; Yeruham Meshel; Chaim Miller; Lou Montenegro and Bernice Perry picketing South African Consulate, 1985; Rafael Martinez; James McCauley
- Nader, Ralph (Box 21, Folder 1)
  Includes Nader speaking at Sales Executives Club
- Nagler, Isadore (Box 21, Folder 2)
  Includes Portrait; Nagler and Herbert Lehman; Nagler with Adolph Held, Jacob Pat and Max Zaritsky
- Nelson, Louis (Box 21, Folder 3)
  Includes Portrait; Nelson speaking at meeting
- Nemaizer, Sam (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Newman, Pauline (Box 21, Folder 5)
  Includes Portraits and individual photos; Newman riding train; Newman at Triangle Fire memorial
- Noto, Salvatore (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Personalities N (Box 21, Folder 7)
  Includes Saby Nehama; Peter Nadash; Morris Novik and Harry Truman, 1959; Fred Noltman; Reinhold Niebur; Salvatore Ninfo
- ONeill, Tip (Box 21, Folder 8)
  Includes Portrait; O'Neil on television with Evelyn Dubrow
- Otto, Sam (Box 21, Folder 9)
  Includes Portrait; Otto and William Ross
- Personalities O (Box 21, Folder 10)
  Includes Edward James Olmos; Ray Orsini; [Lorelion] O'Dwyer; Charles Oronsky
- Perkins, Frances (Box 21, Folder 11)
  Includes Portraits and individual photos; Perkins and Eleanor Roosevelt
- Pesotta, Rose (Box 21, Folder 12)
  Includes Portrait; Pesotta speaking at 1965 convention
- Price, George (Box 21, Folder 13)
  Includes Portraits; Price at table with Pauline Newman and his wife
- Personalities P (Box 21, Folder 14)
  Includes Manager Panetta donating $6,200; Senator William Proxmine; Jacob Potofsky; Herb Pokodner; Abe Plotkin; Esther Peterson; Meyer Perlstein; Dr. Selig Perlman; Judge Jacob Panken; Gerdman Pecora; Morris Palcedino; Joe Piscitello; Aaron Pankin; Steve Perkal
- Pins and Needles (Box 21, Folder 15)
  Includes Program to Upstairs East performance of Pins and Needles actors on stage during performance; Candid shots of actors offstage; Upstairs East entrance
- Presidents of the ILGWU (Box 21, Folder 16)
  Includes Morris Sigman; General Executive Board, 1902;M. W. Schoen, Herman Grossman, James McCauley, Bernard Braff, Benjamin Schlesinger, Sam Bergman and Joseph [Saylor]; Benjamin Schlesinger; Robert M La Follette; David Dubinsky; James McCauley; Congressman Fiorello La Guardia talking to Morris Sigman, 1926; General Executive Board, 1924-25; Sol Chaikin; A. Baroff; Herman Grossman; Abraham Rosenberg; Abraham Cahan
- Presidents of the ILGWU (Box 21, Folder 17)
  Includes Dubinsky and Schelsinger, 1928; Chaikin picketing; Various Portraits and individual photos
- Presidents of the USA (Box 21, Folder 18)
  Includes Franklin Delano Roosevelt; Harry S. Truman; Dwight D. Eisenhower; Lyndon B. Johnson; Luigi Antonini giving Pres. Truman plaque, 1959
- Retired VPs of the ILGWU (Box 21, Folder 19)
  Includes Edward Milano, Charles Zimmerman, E. Howard Molisani, Salvatore Noto and Israel Breslow at the Unity House, 1961
- Quan, Katie (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Quill, Michael (Box 21, Folder 21)
  Includes Portrait; Quill and Jacob Potofsky
- Quintilian, Luigi (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Randolph, Philip (Box 22, Folder 1)
  Includes Portraits; Randolph and Dubinsky
- Reich, Robert (Box 22, Folder 2)
  Includes Portraits and individual photos; At Worker's Memorial Day Celebration; Speaking, with Senator Ted Kennedy looking on
- Reiss, Louis (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Reuther, Walter (Box 22, Folder 4)
  Includes Portraits; Receiving plaque from Eleanor Roosevelt; Reuther with David McDonald, Labor Secretary Mitchell and James Carey
- Rockefeller, Mary (Box 22, Folder 5)
  Includes Rockefeller sewing first Union Label, 1958
- Romney, Edgar (Box 22, Folder 6)
  Includes Portraits; Romney confronting foreman while Tony Rosario, Mike Gomez and Pedro Gonzalez look on, 1976
- Roosevelt, Eleanor (Box 22, Folder 7)
  Includes Mrs. Roosevelt, Dubinsky and Adlai Stevenson; Eleanor Roosevelt threading a needle; Eleanor Roosevelt and Fiorello La Guardia at ILG function; Eleanor Roosevelt with ILGers
- Roosevelt, Franklin Delano (Box 22, Folder 8)
  Includes Cover of Justice, November 1, 1936, Roosevelt Campaign Issue; Roosevelt memorial presented by ILGWU; Shots from "The Roosevelt Story"; Dubinsky and Roosevelt at White House showing of Pins and Needles, 1938
- Ross, William (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Rubenstein, Harry (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Rustin (Box 22, Folder 11)
  Includes Portrait; Speaking at convention
- Personalities R (Box 22, Folder 12)
  Includes Nelson Rockefeller; Sol Chaikin and Abe Raskin, 1983; Congressman Russo, Jay Mazur and Evelyn Dubrow; Abraham Rosenberg; Ralph Reuter; Ada Rose; Alex Rose; James Roosevelt; Julio Ramirez; Samuel Rabinowitz; Abe Raskin; Elias Reisberg; Rendi; Victor Reuther interview by Joe Michaels on WFDR radio, 1951; Abraham Ribicoff; Serafino Romauldi; Mortimer Ritter; Paul Robeson; Congressman Ron Rodino; Nick Roussos; Lou Rolnick; Helen Rooney; Saul Rosen; Anna Rosenberg; Sol Rosenblatt; Harry J. Rubinstein; George Rubin; Gerel [Ruvieu]; Harold Rome; Jack Rubin; Dean Rusk; Frank Rather
- Schlesinger, Benjamin (Box 22, Folder 13)
  Includes Plaque; Portraits
- Schlesinger, Emil (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Schlesinger, Rose (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Schneider, Edward (Box 22, Folder 16)
  Includes Portrait and individual photos
- Schoenwald, Matthew (Box 22, Folder 17)
  Includes Portraits and individual photos
- Schwartz, Bill (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Schwartz, Harold (Box 22, Folder 19)
  Includes Portrait; Schwartz and Morris Bialis
- Schwartz, Henry (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Schwellenbach (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Seaman, B (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Shane, Bernard (Box 22, Folder 23)
  Includes Portrait; Shane with painting of himself; Addressing Cloakmakers Union
- Shore, Samuel (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Shriver, Sargent (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Sigman, Morris (Box 22, Folder 26)
  Includes Portraits; Plaque
- Siems, Fred (Box 22, Folder 27)
  Includes Portraits and individual photos; Siems and Evelyn Dubrow; Siems giving $1,000 to President Harry Truman for Kansas City Philharmonic, 1959
- Solomon, Irwin (Box 23, Folder 1)
  Includes Individual photos; Soloman and Irwin Ladd at United Way benefit; Irwin Soloman, John Riggan and Arnold Wallace; Solomon giving check to Flor Farmington; Solomon and Philadelphia Mayor Frank Rizzo; Solomon, Hermine Hart and Olga Bracey; Solomon, Joseph Fisher and Beatrice Heggs
- Spielman, Lester (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Stein, Leon (Box 23, Folder 3)
  Includes Portraits and individual photos; Stein and Helen Haskel; Stein being interviewed on the street; Stein with Abe Raskin, Meyer Miller, Sol Chaikin and Morris Novik
- Stevenson, Adlai (Box 23, Folder 4)
  Includes Portraits and individual photos; Stevenson and Eleanor Roosevelt; Stevenson with William Green behind
- Stuart, W (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Stulberg, Louis (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Personalities S (Box 23, Folder 7)
  Includes Herman Starobin; Sciuto sworn in by Matthew Schoenwald; Mark Starr; Steichten; Abe Stawer; Louis Stark; Hartford Mayor Spellary; Bebe Stulberg; James Suffrage; Sam Suher; Israel Silverman; Bo Skiri; M. W. Schoen; Joseph Saylem; Boris Shishkin; Isidore Sorkin; Harry Shapiro; Jack Sessions; Indiana Governor Schricken; Abe Schrader; David Schukin; Abe Schlesinger; Walter Schevenels; David J. Saposs; John H Satlonstall; Senator Pierre Salinger; Maida Springer
- Teper, Lazare (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Thomas, Norman (Box 23, Folder 9)
  Includes - Portraits; Thomas cutting birthday cake; Thomas, William Green, Julius Hochman and Luigi Antonini, 1959
- Truman, Harry (Box 23, Folder 10)
  Includes Portrait; Dinner with Truman and David Dubinsky
- Tuvim, Joseph (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Personalities T (Box 23, Folder 12)
  Includes Robert Tilove; Maurice Tobin and Philip Kramer; Carlo Tresca
- Uviller, Harry (Box 23, Folder 13)
  Includes - Portraits; Uviller, Julius Hochman and Freida Miller
- Personalities U (Box 23, Folder 14)
  Includes Actress Liv Ullmann accepting donation from Sol Chaikin; Frederick Umhey; John Ulene
- Vladech, B. (Box 23, Folder 15)
  Includes Vladech speaking
- Vogel, Joshua (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Wagner, Robert (Box 23, Folder 17)
  Includes - Portraits; Wagner presenting NYC Gold Medal of Honor to Herbert Lehman; Wagner and Francis Perkins, 1940
- Wall (Box 23, Folder 18)
  Includes - Portraits; Wall inducting members; Wall at Mondale rally
- Wallace, Henry (Box 23, Folder 19)
  Includes Portrait; Wallace with Pins and Needles cast
- Wander, Henry (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Wells, David (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Weiss, Samuel (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Williams, Harrison (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Windman, Nat (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Wofford, Harris (Box 23, Folder 25)
  Includes Wofford with PA ILGers; Wofford celebrating victory
- Personalities W (Box 23, Folder 26)
  Includes Connie Woodruff; Nathan Wool; Max Wexler; Bernard Weinstern; James J. Wahler; Senator Paul Wellstone; Pres. George Washington; Lillian D. Wald; Harry Wu with Jeff Fiedler and Congressman Tom Lantos; Gladys Weinberg
- Young, Andrew (Box 23, Folder 27)
  Includes Young receiving support from Nicholas Bonanno for mayoral race
- Young, Whitney Jr (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Zametkin, A. (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Zeldin, Samuel (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Zimmerman, Charles (Box 23, Folder 31)
  Includes - Portraits; At christening of boat, "Charles S. Zimmerman"; Zimmerman's wife and son Paul; Zimmerman and Louis Stulberg; Zimmerman and Louis Hyman lead picket, 1926
- Zimny, Max (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Zukerman, Rubin (Box 23, Folder 33)
- American Family Celebration, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  May 14
- Nancy Brown (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Sol Chaikin (Box 24, Folder 3)
- China--Lu Jingua, dissident (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Chinese New Year, Buddhist Temple, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  January
- Ralph Fasanella, Local 89-22-1, Brooklyn shop (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Jim Tynan's--Ralph Fasanella at Gracie Mansion (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Samuel Gompers addressing strike meeting, Cooper Union, 1909 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  November 22
- History--ILG, Justice (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Import Rally, Washington, D.C., 1990 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  September 12
- ILGWU Convention, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  Includes Hillary Clinton and Ted Kennedy
- ILGWU Fashion Show (Box 24, Folder 12)
- ILG March on Washington, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- ILGWU Quilt (Box 24, Folder 14)
- President Lyndon B. Johnson rally, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Justice (Box 24, Folder 16)
  1960s and 1970s
- Justice (Box 24, Folder 17)
  1970s
- Justice (Box 24, Folder 18)
  1980s
- Justice (Box 24, Folder 19)
- LC Interview--Geraldine Wiley-Bob Gumpert (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Local 23-25 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Los Angeles Guess? Action (Box 24, Folder 22)
  Photos by Ed Carreon, arrest of Tom Morello of Rage Against the Machine
- Nelson Mandela visit, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  [New York City]
- Monarch Fire, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  March
- No NAFTA demonstration with Biana Jagger (Box 24, Folder 25)
  November 10, 1993?
- School visit, 4th grade class (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Early strikes, other demonstrations (Box 24, Folder 27)
- 1920s--2nd battle with Communists and 1926 strike (Box 24, Folder 28)
- "Tenement" photos (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Union Department. AIM (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Union Health Center (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Unity House Murals (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Workers Center Rally, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  June 18
- AFL-CIO (1), Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO (2), Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO (3), Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Archives, Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Canada (1), Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Canada (2), Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Canada (3), Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Canada (1), Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Canada (2), Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Central States, Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Chaikin, Sol, Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Convention, 1949, Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Convention, 1977 (1), Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Convention, 1977 (2), Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Convention, 1980 (1), Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Convention, 1980 (2), Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Convention, 1980 (3), Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Convention, 1980 (4), Black and white photograph (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Convention, 1980 (1), Black and white photograph (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Convention, 1980 (2), Black and white photograph (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Convention, 1980 (3), Black and white photograph (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Convention, 1980 (4), Black and white photograph (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Convention, 1980 (5), Black and white photograph (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Convention, 1980 (1), Black and white photograph (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Convention, 1980 (2), Black and white photograph (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Convention, 1980 (3), Black and white photograph (Box 26, Folder 8)
- NYC High School of Fashion Industries, Ernest Fiene Murals, Black and white photograph (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Northeast, Black and white photograph (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Puerto Rico (1), Black and white photograph (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Puerto Rico (2), Black and white photograph (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Retirees, Black and white photograph (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Southeast Region, Black and white photograph (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Union Health Center, Black and white photograph (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Union Label, Black and white photograph (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Union Privileges, Black and white photograph (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Union Yes, Black and white photograph (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Unity House, Black and white photograph (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Upper South, Black and white photograph (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Warehouse Workers, Black and white photograph (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Western States (1), Black and white photograph (Box 27, Folder 7)